

- Boom Mic Operator
- Camera Operator
- Stagehand







#### CONTACT

222 Elm St Washington MO, 63090

TELEPH: (636)-266-9151

EMAIL: hooklightprod@gmail.com WEBSITE: hooklightproductions.com

YOUTUBE James Wacker
INSTAGRAM @james\_wacker\_
LINKEDIN James Wacker

#### SKILLS

### PROFESSIONAL:

- Independant self-starter
- Great on a team
- Attention to detail

### TECHNICAL:

- Sound recording for film
- · Camera skills for live events and film
- Setup and run with video switchers

## PERSONAL GEAR

- Sound Devices Mix-Pre 6 II
- Black Magic Desing Pocket Cinema 4K

### SUMMARY

I'm a student at Webster University enrolled in the Film, Television, and Video Production program. I specalize as a boom mic operator for film, but I also have extensive experience running cameras, lighting scenes, operating live video switchers, and sound mixers. As a freelancer I've worked on live events, weddings, small commercial shoots, and short films. Currently I'm working through IATSE Local 6 in St. Louis as a stagehand setting up concerts and as a camera operator for concerts, corporate seminars, and other live events.

#### EDUCATION

#### WEBSTER UNIVERSITY

2020-Present

#### FILM, TELEVISION, & VIDEO PRODUCTION

I'm currently enrolled at Webster working toward my undergraduate degree in film, television, and video production.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

STAGEHAND / CAMERA OP 2022-Present

#### IATSE LOCAL 6 / 1611 S Broadway St, Unit 110, Saint Louis MO

As a stagehand I set up LED video walls, PA speakers, lighting trusses, and stage decks. I've also set up and ran cameras for various concerts and corporate events.

# B CAMERA / SOUND MIXER 2018-2019, 2023- Present

#### CHIMERA CREATIVE WORKS / 319 Elm St, Washington MO

I've worked with the owner Steven Lyles as a B-camera on several small commercial shoots for area businesses. I've also done live sound mixing for small corporate seminars.

# LIVESTREAM PRODUCER / LIVE SWITCHER 2020-Present

#### ST. PETER'S UCC, WASHINGTON MO / 20 E Fifth St, Washington MO

I started working at St. Peter's in 2020 because they needed assistance to broadcast their services during the pandemic. I began using my own equipment but over the past three years I've helped transition them to a simple live switcher system and trained another technician to operate it